so I joined a book club that might favor
one of my favorite authors and speakers
is putting on and I have called the book
is called the illusion of money and the
speaker / writer is Kyle sees he's
awesome
highly recommended the one thing that I
don't agree with him on is money so why
I chose to join a book club about money
I don't know except that it brought me
this it brought me to the point where
right now I am taking a vow of abundance
and what that means to me like I know
what he says about wealth when he said
on the weekends and the phone call was
basically like your own inner thoughts
and beliefs and stories were what's
keeping you from for money and most of
what he says in the book and most of
what he talks about is very powerful and
important but he's like like you're the
one who's stopping you from getting 100
million dollars a month and like that is
an OK and obtainable goal and not only
is that not an obtainable goal for the
vast majority of people it's also very
much not not everyone can have that that
is by design scarcity money is designed
to be scarce and so it is TruGreen for
me I really don't like it when all of
the self-help people in all of the
spiritual community is talks about money
like it's the source of spirit and
energy when it is a tool that is used
it's not designed to be that it's
designed to be scarce abundance is not
that abundance there's enough food on
this planet for everybody there is
enough space on this planet there are
enough resources if we don't use them up
for stupid stupid things and we take
care of our planet there is enough for
anyone and everyone so I am NOT nor will
I ever take a vow to get and gain and
hoard money in foreign only me it's not
what I'm here to do I'm here to do the
opposite of that but nor do I need to
take a vow of poverty and those seems to
be my only two options before now I've
been
living this what I'm talking about
without there being a word for it so I'm
taking a vow of abundance I am allowing
the universe the circumstances to give
me what they want to give me whether
that's in monetary form or not but I'm
not seeking it out for monetary form I'm
not looking to do things to get
exchanged for money and I'm not looking
to to buy things for money I'm looking
for ways to contribute that Carl that
call to me that make me happy and I'm
looking for looking for his wrong word
I'm open to what the universe and other
people are looking to give me and so I'm
taking a vow of abundance because the
more of us that take a vow of abundance
the better because as we live in that
space of being open to what we're being
given and creating and giving what we're
what we have to give the more it calls
other people into that abundance of one
creates abundance for all and abundance
of all creates abundance for you whereas
I'm sorry wealth and money do not work
that way
so that is today's video I am taking a
vow of abundance and I invite you to do
the same